The Candy Kings
糖果国王
Once candy was not made for children.
以前糖果不是为儿童做的
In one country, almost 5000 years ago,
在一个国家  近5000年前
candy was made only for kings.
糖果只为国王而做
Today, children are the candy kings.
如今  孩子们是糖果国王
Have you ever eaten licorice?
你吃过甘草吗
People in ancient times ate licorice, too.
人们在古代也吃甘草
They did think of licorice as candy at first.
一开始他们认为甘草是糖果
They ate licorice to keep them strong and well.
他们吃甘草来保持强壮和健康
In some countries, people ate licorice to make them beautiful!
在一些国家  人们吃了甘草使他们变得漂亮
Later, people ate it just because it tasted good!
后来  人们吃它只是因为它味道好
All candy was made by hand until 1845.
直到1845年  所有糖果是手工做的,
In that year, a man made a candy machine.
那一年  一个男人做了一个糖果机
By the 1900s, candy was sold all over the world.
1900年代  糖果被销往世界各地
Today, candy companies say a person eats from 15 to 30 pounds of candy a year.
如今  糖果公司说一个人一年要吃15到30磅的糖果
More than 2000 different kinds of candy are made!
制作了超过2000个不同种类的糖果
How many kinds do you eat, candy king?
你吃了多少种  糖果国王